David Maldonado

301 Belcher Rd N apt. 1104•Largo, FL 33771•(727)249-3080 david.m.maldonado@gmail.com http://dave-maldonado.github.io

Executive Summary

More than 10 years of customer-facing call center experience in both technical support and non-technical customer service roles. More than 10 years of personal experience troubleshooting PC issues and three years of personal experience programming.

Skills

•Ruby •Rails •Java •Linux •PC repair •troubleshooting

Education

University of South Florida

expected class of 2016

- admitted for the Fall 2013 semester
- studying Computer Science
- regular participant of the Tampa Ruby and Codernight meetups

Hillsborough Community College

class of 2012

- graduated with an Associate of Arts and a 3.3 GPA
- took 2 courses in Java programming and a course in PC hardware
- joined Suncoast Linux User's Group (SLUG)

Wesley Chapel High School

class of 2001

Selected Work Experience

Verifone Inc. - Clearwater, FL

2012-present

• providing technical assistance to users of stand-alone credit card terminals and point-of-sale transaction software

Marcone Part Supply - Tampa, FL

2010-2012

 \bullet assisted customers in obtaining the major appliance parts required to perform repairs

Macy's Inc. - Clearwater, FL

2007-2010

• provided technical support for the Macys.com website

Safe Pest Control - Seminole, FL

2005-2007

• responsible for a route encompassing Pinellas, Hillsborough and Pasco counties